// src/data/wnbaPlayersColleges.js
export default [
  { front: "A'ja Wilson", back: "South Carolina" },     // Breanna Stewart :contentReference[oaicite:5]{index=5}
  { front: "Chelsea Gray", back: "Duke" },              // Chelsea Gray :contentReference[oaicite:7]{index=7}
  { front: "Alyssa Thomas", back: "Maryland" },         // Alyssa Thomas :contentReference[oaicite:9]{index=9}
  { front: "Jewell Loyd", back: "Notre Dame" },         // Jewell Loyd :contentReference[oaicite:11]{index=11}
  { front: "Kelsey Plum", back: "Washington" },         // Kelsey Plum :contentReference[oaicite:13]{index=13}
  { front: "Brittney Griner", back: "Baylor" },         // Brittney Griner :contentReference[oaicite:15]{index=15}
  { front: "Sabrina Ionescu", back: "Oregon" },         // Sabrina Ionescu :contentReference[oaicite:17]{index=17}
  { front: "Candace Parker", back: "Tennessee" },       // Diana Taurasi :contentReference[oaicite:21]{index=21}
  { front: "Kelsey Mitchell", back: "Ohio State" },         // Maya Moore :contentReference[oaicite:25]{index=25}
  { front: "Nneka Ogwumike", back: "Stanford" },  
  { front: "Caitlin CLark", back: "Iowa"},
  { front: "Napheesa Collier", back: "Connecticut"}     // Tina Charles :contentReference[oaicite:29]{index=29}
];
